; This file uses Windows Unicode (UC2) encoding
;
; Banner is a text shown to all universe.
; Interval between banners can be specified in FLShel.ini (default is 15 min).
; Each line in the file represents one banner.
; Banners can be in any language.
; Amount of banners is not limited as well as banner length.
;
Welcome to our server! This server is cool because it's running FLShell and Flak's 88 FLHook :)
Rules: No insults, begging and cheating. No allies and neutrals attack without warning.
Each Bad Player will be warned->killed->kicked->bastiplaced->banned for a day->banned for a week->permanently banned
To see list of console commands run /? or /help command.
List of all RP restarts - run /dots. NOTE: Restart working only after creating fresh char.
Is desirable to create nick in form "nick.name". Char with Non-latinnic or servercrashable nick may be permanently banned.
Admins are using differents nicks in game, so be good boy/girl, we are watching you.