; This file uses Windows Unicode (UC2) encoding
;
; All this text will be shown to just logged in player.
; It can be in any language.
; No limits for the text but think about screen size. 
;
Hi, mate! Nice to see you here.
This server is cool and running FLShell.
To see list of console commands run /? or /help command.

Rules: No insults, begging and cheating. No allies and neutrals attack without warning.
Each Bad Player will be warned->killed->kicked->bastiplaced->banned for a day->banned for a week->permanently banned

Be careful! Death in PvP costs money now. You have been warned.

List of all RP restarts - run /dots. NOTE: Restart working only after creating fresh char.

Is desirable to create nick in form "nick.name". Char with Non-latinnic or servercrashable nick may be permanently banned.

Admins are using differents nicks in game, so be good boy/girl, we are watching you.

All questions write at our forum http://dod.the-starport.ru/forum !